nigerianseminarsandtrainings.com 2017-02-23

# Privacy Policy - Nigerian Seminars and Trainings

This privacy policy sets out how Nigerian Seminars and Trainings.com (subsequent referred to as us/we) uses and protects any information that you give to us when you use this website.  
Nigerian Seminars and Trainings.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. If we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website; you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
Nigerian Seminars and Trainings.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require the information we collect to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information we collect to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you have not indicated that you do not wish this to happen.  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at [admin@nigerianseminarsandtrainings.com](mailto:admin@nigerianseminarsandtrainings.com "email address") or [info@nigerianseminarsandtrainings.com](mailto:info@nigerianseminarsandtrainings.com "email address"). We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
